# **Conner Linzy**

# Full-Stack Web Developer

Charlotte, NC (willing to relocate)

conner.linzy.dev@gmail.com • LinkedIn • 321-830-2074 • connerlinzy.com/

## Summary of Qualifications

Fullstack web developer specializing in MERN stack architecture with 1+ years of experience. Highly effective and independent problem solver. Proven leadership and project management capabilities in previous roles, as well as successfully implementing company-wide policies and productivity systems in a startup. Commended for independence, excellent communication, and meticulous problem-solving. Driven by a desire to reach my full potential in a technical field.

## Accomplishments

- Passed Hatchways fullstack project interview with minimal backend experience, received excellent feedback.
- Built 10+ active projects with a wide array of technologies, both alone and on open-source teams.
- Developed a system for coordination of monthly maintenance for 50+ commercial irrigation systems, involving an average of 15 employees, from the ground up.
  Successfully maintained and improved the system for 3 years.

#### Skills

- Careful state management with pure functions
- Understanding of deeper Javascript concepts like closure, prototypal inheritance, and function/object composition
- UI / UX and user-centered design
- Consistent documentation style with JSDoc
- 100% responsive and cross-browser design
- Fullstack debugging with understanding of the JS engine and runtime
- Performance considerations for UX and emissions, often in regards to the React render cycle, or API consumption
- Integrating and familiarizing myself with a new codebase in a timely manner
- Understanding of git collaboration workflows

# Technologies

- Front End: HTML CSS Javascript React Redux SASS Mobile Dev Bootstrap
- Back End: Node.js Express MongoDB PostgreSQL Firebase OAuth Sockets
- Build Tools: Typescript Git Unit Tests NPM Jest JSDoc Webpack

# Experience

### **Delivery Driver**

Fedex Ground | Nov 2020 - Mar 2021 | Asheville, NC

- Delivered packages to 100 150 locations per day
- Assisted other drivers in loading and delivering packages

#### Supervisor

BlueH2O Irrigation | 2017 - 2020 | Melbourne. FL

- Maintenance coordination of 50+ commercial irrigation systems
- Planned, proposed, and coordinated projects for commercial contractors and residential customers, including administration and follow-up service
- Diagnosed field issues, including low and high voltage electricity, buried cable fault locating, centrifugal pump repair, electrical timers, plumbing, and locating water leaks
- Billing, payroll, inventory management, on-site supervision, scheduling work, general employee management

## Line Cook / Manager

Kelsey's Pizzeria | 2012 - 2017 | Melbourne. FL

- Coordinated of front and back of house service
- Coordinated deliveries
- Created new menu items
- Ordered and tracked inventory

## Education

#### **Western Governors University**

Bachelor of Science in Software Development | Anticipated Graduation: 2022 | Salt Lake City, UT

#### Relevant courses:

- User Interface Design built portfolio site and received the CIW UI Designer Certification
- User Experience Design built a wireframe and prototype for a tourism site, conducted and participated in usability tests with other students.
- Data Management & Database Design learned relational database best practices and schema design, normalized databases, wrote effective queries.

#### Certifications

- CompTIA A+ ce Certification Issued Sep 2020
- ITIL Foundation Level Issued Oct 2020
- CIW User Interface Designer Issued Jan 2021
- CIW Site Development Associate Issued Nov 2020
- The Complete Web Developer in 2021 Zero To Mastery Academy Issued Jan 2020